JAKUB MICHALSKI

.NET DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a third-year computer science student, interested in programming for over four years. I have six months of experience as a .NET developer. My goal is to improve my software engineering skills and gain experience in .NET and web development.

KNOWN TECHNOLOGIES

- -C#/.NET
- -ASD NET
- -Entity Framework
- -SQL Server
- -xUnit
- -Javascript
- -jQuery
- -Typescript
- -HTMI
- -CSS/SASS
- -Bootstrap
- -Reac
- -\\/DE
- -GIT
- -Azure DevOps

LANGUAGES

Polish - native English - B2

CONTACT DETAILS

jakubmichalski01@gmail.com

LINKS

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Github</u> Codewars

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer Intern

Freeport Metrics (7.2023 - 9.2023)

- Working on CRM system for credit card payment industry
- Developing code in C#/ASP.NET MVC
- Writing unit and integration tests
- Collecting and analyzing client's business requirements

Junior .NET developer (internship)

TRUMPF Huettinger (7.2022 - 9.2022)

- Developed desktop applications using WinForms and WPF frameworks
- During internship I have created the app "Dynamic Smith Chart", which main function was to visualize the impedance of electrical device. The app has been appreciated by company's engineers, who started to use it in everyday work

EDUCATION

Uczelnia Techniczno-Handlowa im. Heleny Chodkowskiej

Computer science, specialization - software engineering (10.2021 - now)

- Member of computer science club "Koło wzajemnej kompilacji"
- Taken part in two scientific conferences as a speaker
- Received President of University scholarship for academic years 2021/2022 and 2022/2023
- Thesis: "Visualization of Mandelbrot set"

PROJECTS

Quizz

- Web application for creating and solving quizes
- Account creation, user authorization, REST API communication, SQL Server database
- Stack: ASP.NET, Entity Framework, SQL Server, React.js, Typescript
- Github: Michu01/QuizApi (github.com) (api), Michu01/quizclient (github.com) (front)

Rubik Cube Solver

- Desktop app for solving Rubik's Cube
- Has an implementation of Thisthlethwaite's algorithm, which solves any cube in at most 45 moves
- Stack: C#/.Net, WPF
- Github: Michu01/RubikCubeSolverApp (github.com)

Robotic Arm GUI

- Robotic arm set "Braccio Tinkerkit" based on Arduino microcontroller, steered with PS4 console controller
- Graphical user interface written in C#/WPF, allows user to write programs for the robotic arm
- Github: Michu01/RobotArmApp (github.com)

HOBBIES

Solving algorithmic problems, web development, robotics (Arduino), computer graphics, cycling, tourism, rock and heavy metal music